shoptimate.com 2019-08-28

# Privacy policy - Shoptimate.com

The privacy policy covers the use of Shoptimate ("Shoptimate), a browser extension (the "Extension") and this website and any sub-sites herof (the "Site") which are published and maintained by Sourcefully SPRL. This helps you understand what information is collected when you use the extension or site and how we use that information. By downloading the extension or using the site, you confirm that you have read and agree to the terms of this policy. 

## Collected information

We try to reduce the information that we collect to a strict minimum. 

For each page that your visit on our servers, we can collect the following information in the server logs: 

  * Page URL
  * Browser Information (user agent)
  * IP address

For every click to a merchant product page, we can on top collect the following information: 

  * The originating page
  * The destination page
  * The product details

When you create an account, we collect: 

  * Your contact information
  * If you have a price alert, the list of products for which you requested a price alert and the threshold price

## How do we use the information

The information collected is used to improve our service and detect fraud and abuse. We do not rent or sell your personal information to any third party. 

## Data retention

Any information used for statistics and fraud detection is kept for up to a year. We may store aggregated and non-personnal data for a longer period than 12 months for financial and statistical reasons.

## Contact us

Upon request, we will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. You may access or request deletion of your personal information by contacting us. We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe.

Last updated: May 21 2018
